A Guide to the Walter Wyatt Papers
University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library, #10278-d
Walter Wyatt Papers 1918-1944
University of Virginia. Library. Special Collections Dept. Alderman Library University of Virginia Charlottesville, Virginia 22903 USA
10278-d
ca. 700 items
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
Bequest, 1989 October 4
Container List
- Personal Correspondence and Papers
  - Correspondence of the Graves and Wyatt families, and related papers, 1918-1938, n.d. (Box Box 1)
  - Letters to Walter and Allie (Graves) Wyatt from Mrs. Robert A. Graves, 1918-1937, n.d.; (5 folders) (Box Box 1)
- Federal Reserve Board Papers
  - Federal Reserve Board, 1920-1923; (2 folders) (Box Box 1)
  - Federal Reserve Board, 1924-1948; (4 folders) (Box Box 2)
  - Federal Reserve Board, n.d. (Box Box 3)
  - Federal Reserve Board: Newspaper Articles, 1930-1944 (Box Box 3)
  - Federal Reserve Board: Reviews--Newspapers and Periodicals, 1926 (Box Box 3)
  - Federal Reserve Board: Summaries of Press Comments, 1935 Feb-June; (2 folders) (Box Box 3)